{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": {
        "theme": [
          {
            "Question": "Which animated series features a group of toddlers in a playpen?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Rugrats",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "SpongeBob SquarePants",
              "The Flintstones",
              "The Jetsons"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Rugrats follows the adventures of a group of babies and their day-to-day lives in the fictional town of 'Hillwood'. It ran for nine seasons from 1991 to 2004."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the secret identity of the crime-fighting duo from 'The Powerpuff Girls'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Professor Utonium",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Mojo Jojo",
              "HIM",
              "Mayor of Townsville"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Professor Utonium accidentally created the Powerpuff Girls using a mixture of sugar, spice, everything nice, and Chemical X in his laboratory."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In 'Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles', who is the leader of the group?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Leonardo",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Raphael",
              "Donatello",
              "Michelangelo"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Leonardo is the courageous and disciplined leader of the Ninja Turtles, often seen wielding two katanas in battle."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which cartoon character owns a pet dog named Odie?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Garfield",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Scooby-Doo",
              "Goofy",
              "Daffy Duck"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Garfield, created by Jim Davis, is known for his love of lasagna and his disdain for Mondays and exercise, and for bullying his canine companion, Odie."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who is the main villain in 'He-Man and the Masters of the Universe'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Skeletor",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Hordak",
              "Beast Man",
              "Trap Jaw"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Skeletor, the archenemy of He-Man, is a blue-skinned sorcerer with a skull for a face and a hooded robe. He seeks to conquer Castle Grayskull to gain its secrets."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which character pilots the ThunderTank in 'ThunderCats'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Panthro",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Lion-O",
              "Cheetara",
              "Tygra"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Panthro, the strong and agile ThunderCat, is the chief mechanic who pilots the ThunderTank and is known for his exceptional fighting skills and strategic mind."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the theme song for 'DuckTales'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "DuckTales Theme",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Life is like a hurricane",
              "TailSpin",
              "Darkwing Duck"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The 'DuckTales Theme' is an iconic tune originally written by Mark Mueller and performed by Jeff Pescetto for the animated TV show 'DuckTales'."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which cartoon character says the catchphrase 'What's up, Doc?'",
            "TrueAnswer": "Bugs Bunny",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Scooby-Doo",
              "Mickey Mouse",
              "Tom Cat"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Bugs Bunny is an iconic character known for his nonchalant demeanor, clever quips, and the catchphrase 'What's up, Doc?'"
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the superhero alter ego of Dexter in 'Dexter's Laboratory'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Action Dexter",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Captain Justice",
              "Mega Dexter",
              "Power Dexter"
            ],
            "Explanation": "In the episode 'Village of the D'Urps,' Dexter gains superpowers and becomes 'Action Dexter,' a parody of superhero tropes as he fights villains like 'The Silver Spooner.'"
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which character is the main antagonist in 'The Smurfs'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Gargamel",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Azrael",
              "Papa Smurf",
              "Smurfette"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Gargamel, an evil sorcerer, is the perpetual nemesis of the Smurfs, constantly seeking to capture and destroy them to create a potion for ultimate power."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the cat owned by the Powerpuff Girls' neighbor, Professor Utonium?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Mochi",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Boots",
              "Waffles",
              "Fluffy"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Mochi is an intelligent and curious pet cat owned by Professor Utonium and often seen interacting with the Powerpuff Girls and their adventures."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which 80s cartoon centers around a group of bear siblings with magical abilities?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Care Bears",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Gummi Bears",
              "Yogi Bear",
              "We Bare Bears"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The Care Bears are a group of cuddly bears with various magical powers who live in the clouds at Care-a-Lot, spreading love and positivity."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Who is the genius canine inventor in 'Droopy, Master Detective'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "McWolf",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Dripple",
              "Spike",
              "Droopy"
            ],
            "Explanation": "McWolf, a villain who is also an inventor, creates diabolical gadgets and schemes to outwit Droopy and his son, Dripple, in their detective adventures."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the fictional world in 'The Smurfs'?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Smurf Village",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Gargamel's Lair",
              "Enchanted Forest",
              "Whispering Meadows"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Smurf Village is the woodland home of the Smurfs, situated in a hidden, secluded location to avoid the clutches of Gargamel."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the name of the monkey in 'Dexter's Laboratory' who has a penchant for chaos?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Monkey",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Rafael",
              "Steve",
              "Charlie"
            ],
            "Explanation": "The character simply known as 'Monkey' possesses superhuman intelligence and strength, often aiding Dexter or causing mayhem through his mischievous antics."
          },
          {
            "Question": "What is the superhero name of the crime-fighting alter ego of Doug Funnie?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Quailman",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Crimson Chin",
              "Darkwing Duck",
              "Mighty Mouse"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Doug Funnie's superhero alter ego, Quailman, sports a belt and underpants over his clothing and fights injustice and wrongs in his imaginative alter-ego adventures."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In 'The Jetsons', what is the name of the robot maid who takes care of the family?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Rosie",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Jane",
              "Judy",
              "Elroy"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Rosie is the highly capable and personable household robot maid employed by the Jetson family, tasked with maintaining the household and caring for the family's needs."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which animated series features a blue hedgehog with super speed?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Sonic the Hedgehog",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Road Runner",
              "Stuart Little",
              "Mighty Mouse"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Sonic the Hedgehog is known for his high-speed adventures, ability to curl into a ball, and ongoing conflict with the villainous Dr. Robotnik."
          },
          {
            "Question": "In 'Inspector Gadget', who is the mastermind behind the protagonist's array of gadgets?",
            "TrueAnswer": "Chief Quimby",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Dr. Claw",
              "Penny",
              "Brain"
            ],
            "Explanation": "Chief Quimby, the head of the secret police department, is responsible for providing Inspector Gadget with his gadgets and assignments while remaining incognito."
          },
          {
            "Question": "Which animated series features the adventures of a smooth-talking cat and a gullible dog?",
            "TrueAnswer": "CatDog",
            "FalseAnswer": [
              "Ren & Stimpy",
              "Tom & Jerry",
              "Sylvester & Tweety"
            ],
            "Explanation": "CatDog follows the daily misadventures of a conjoined twin hybrid, the upper body of a cat and the lower body of a dog, navigating their contrasting personalities and experiences."
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  ]
}